<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>Rock NYC.org RSS Feed</title>
  <link>https://rocknyc.org</link>
  <description>Latest articles from Rock NYC.org</description>
  
<!-- important notes section -->
<!-- <p> -->
<!-- <![CDATA[  ]]> -->
<!-- https://rocknyc.org/rss.xml -->



 <item>
    <title>Wolfgang Van Halen: Lessons from Rock Royalty and Hitting the Stage with Mammoth</title>
    <link>https://rocknyc.org/</link>
    <description>
    <![CDATA[
<body>

<h1>Wolfgang Van Halen: Rocking Out of His Dad's Shadow and Into the Mammoth Limelight</h1>

<p>Wolfgang Van Halen, who once rocked the bass with the iconic Van Halen, is now making waves with his own gig, Mammoth WVH. After the legendary Eddie Van Halen passed in 2020, Wolfgang revealed his heart-wrenching tribute "Distance" under Mammoth WVH, setting the stage for their debut album in 2021. And guess what, rockers? Like the legends Dave Grohl and Prince, Wolfgang jammed every instrument on that album! With his latest masterpiece, "Mammoth II", out now and the crew touring alongside Metallica, Wolfgang took a moment with Rolling Stone to drop some wisdom from his Van Halen days.</p>

<p>"With Van Halen, I learned a lot of how I didn’t want things to be with Mammoth. Why do we need to be walking around on eggshells? Why is there a problem all the time? Like, why can’t we just get along and play music? Don’t we all love music enough to put our bullshit aside and actually have a good time having this be our livelihood? Shouldn’t it be easier than this?" he reflected. Wolfgang's mission for Mammoth? A rock-solid team that's all about the tunes and can ride through any storm. And here's a fun tidbit: Wolfgang might just try his hand at other instruments on stage in the future. Rock on, Wolfgang!</p>

</body>
    ]]>
    </description>
    <image></image>
  </item>









  <item>
    <title>Mick Fleetwood's Maui Retreat Devastated by Wildfires</title>
    <link>https://rocknyc.org/</link>
    <description><![CDATA[

    
        <p style="font-size: 10px; text-align: center;">(Artist Rendering, Not Actual Event)</p>
        </br>
    
    <p>Mick Fleetwood's beloved Hawaiian establishment, Fleetwood's on Front Street, has tragically been claimed by the escalating wildfires in Maui.

<p>The fires kicked off several days ago, leading to the evacuation of thousands. As the flames advance, 36 individuals tragically lost their lives, with entire neighborhoods reduced to cinders. The origins of this firestorm remain unclear.

<p>Mick Fleetwood, the rhythmic force behind Fleetwood Mac and a long-time Maui dweller, founded Fleetwood's on Front Street in 2012. Addressing the situation, he stated, "Maui and the Lahaina community have been my home for several decades. This is a devastating moment for Maui, and many are suffering unimaginable loss. Fleetwood's on Front Street has been lost and while we are heartbroken, our main priority is the safety of our dear staff and team members."

<p>The restaurant's official channels also reached out, noting, "As most of you know Maui has been dealing with extreme fires created by the residual winds of Hurricane Dora. Lahaina Town has taken the brunt of it. ... Mahalo for your continued thoughts and prayers for our community and our first responders."

<p>Concluding with heartfelt sentiment, Mick Fleetwood shared, "On behalf of myself and my family, I share my heartfelt thoughts and prayers for the people of Maui." Let's not forget other renowned artists like Steven Tyler and Willie Nelson also have roots in Hawaii, and they, too, are feeling the impact.
</p>
]]>
</description>
<image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/musicis3965/rockNYC/main/articleImages/article1Image.png</image>
    
  </item>
<!-- new item -->
<!-- ----------------- -->
<!-- ----------------- -->

  <item>
    <title>Trisha, Keith and All-Stars Gear Up for ACM Honors!</title>
    <link>https://rocknyc.org/</link>
    <description>
    <![CDATA[
   

<head>
    <meta charset="UTF-8">
    <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0">
    <title>Rock On! ACM Honors Lineup Announcement</title>
    <style>
        body {
            font-family: Arial, sans-serif;
        }

        h1 {
            color: #333;
            text-align: center;
        }

        p {
            margin: 15px 0;
        }

        .highlight {
            color: #ff4500;
        }
    </style>
</head>

<body>

   <p>
        Heads up, rockers! Country music's heavy hitters like <span class="highlight">Trisha Yearwood</span>, <span class="highlight">Keith Urban</span>, <span class="highlight">Breland</span>, and <span class="highlight">Chris Janson</span> are ready to light up the stage at the 16th annual ACM Honors, straight from the Academy's lips.
    </p>

    <p>
        But wait, there's more! We've got Bailey Zimmerman, Jordan Davis, Emily Shackelton, and rockin' groups like <span class="highlight">Lady A</span>, The War and Treaty, and more joining the jam at the legendary Ryman Auditorium in Nashville on August 23. Stay tuned, cause the full TV lineup's gonna drop soon!
    </p>

    <p>
        ACM's head honcho, <span class="highlight">Damon Whiteside</span>, promises a night to remember: “filled with emotional tributes and unforgettable performances… An undeniable highlight for our Country Music community this fall.”
    </p>

    <p>
        Dubbed the "ultimate country music bash," the ACM Honors salute the big shots making waves in country tunes. On the list this year? Legends like <span class="highlight">Chris Stapleton</span>, Tim McGraw, and more. <span class="highlight">Carly Pearce</span> is back as the hostess with the mostest for the third year running.
    </p>

    <p>
        Mark your calendars, party people! The ACM Honors airs September 18, 8 p.m. ET on FOX. Missed it? No sweat, catch the replay on Hulu the next day. Rock on! 🎸🔥
    </p>

</body>




    ]]>
    </description>
    <image></image>
  </item>

<!--  -->
<!-- ----------------- -->
<!-- ----------------- -->

 


<!-- new item -->
<!-- ----------------- -->
<!--

  <item>
    <title>put headline here</title>
    <link>https://rocknyc.org/</link>
    <description>
    <![CDATA[
put HTML here
    ]]>
    </description>
    <image></image>
  </item>

  -->

  <!--  -->
<!-- ----------------- -->
<!-- ----------------- -->

</channel>
</rss>
